Guide to the Rice University Student Association records, 1918-2013 UA 252
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Student Association records
1918-2013
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University. Student Association
UA 252
15 Linear Feet (30 Boxes)
1.11 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_001 (1.11 GB)
1.10 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_002 (1.10 GB)
0.10 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_003 (0.10 GB)
0.371 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_004 (0.371 GB)
0.625 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_005 (0.625 GB)
0.109 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_006 (0.109 GB)
0.295 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_007 (0.295 GB)
17.0 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_008 (17.0 GB)
7.85 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_009 (7.85 GB)
1.53 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_010 (1.53 GB)
19.2 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_011 (19.2 GB)
16.5 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_012 (16.5 GB)
0.298 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0252aip_013 (0.298 GB)
The Student Association Records consist of a variety of material related to the Rice University Student Association. These records include meeting minutes, correspondence, memos, constitution and bylaws, financial documents, floor plans, reports, employee contracts, proposals, and student publications. The material begins in 1918 and continues through 2013, with the bulk of the information starting in the early 1960s.
Biographical/Historical Note
The Student Association formed through vote during a mass meeting of the student body on December 12, 1918. Lead by senior class president H. L. Bell, the first regular meeting of the Rice University Student Association was held on January 25, 1919 in the Physics building at 1:30 P.M. The association then proceeded to draft a constitution and to deal with problems concerning funds for school activites and organizations, including the Thresher and the Campanile.
The Student Association has contributed not only to the daily workings of Rice University, but also the overall culture and experience felt by today's students. In 1969, the Student Association fought for the readmition of Rice University's first African-American student and, in 1973, petitioned to provide legal consultation for all Rice students. Since its formation, the Student Association continued to support student speech, social outreach, and to keep the student body politically informed.
Today, the Student Association is run by an elected Senate consisting of the Executive committee, the college Senators, and the college Presidents. The Student Association's goal is to be "the voice of the student body and a forum for students to help students make improvements in student life". Please see sa.rice.edu for more information.
Scope and Contents
The Student Association Records consist of a variety of material related to the Rice University Student Association. These records include meeting minutes, correspondence, memos, constitution and bylaws, financial documents, floor plans, reports, employee contracts, proposals, and student publications. The material begins in 1918 and continues through 2013, with the bulk of the information starting in the early 1960s.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to the Woodson Research Center primarily in March 1990 by Mary Elliot as well as in July 2000 by Lindsay Botsford. Additional materials were transferred in 2016.
Arrangement
These records are arranged in fifteen series with the following titles: General, Committees, Constitution and Bylaws, Correspondence and Memos, Financial, Judicial, Organizations, Pub, Publications, Colleges, Rice Program Council, and Minutes. An addenda was added in 2016.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Social life and customs; Rice University -- History; Politics and government
Document Types
minutes (administrative records); letters (correspondence)
Places
Rice University
- Series I: General, 146400
  - Aggie Parody (Halftime Performance), 1973; 146401 (Box 1a, Folder 1)
  - Alumni: Committees, 1970-1971; 146402 (Box 1a, Folder 2)
  - Alumni, General, 1972; 146403 (Box 1a, Folder 3)
  - Athletics, General, 1972-1982; 146404 (Box 1a, Folder 4)
  - Automated Teller, 1984-1987; 146405 (Box 1a, Folder 5)
  - Basketball, 1971-1972; 146406 (Box 1a, Folder 6)
  - Board of Governors and Associates, 1970-1975; 146407 (Box 1a, Folder 7)
  - [George R.] Brown Dinner Demonstration, 1975; 146408 (Box 1a, Folder 8)
  - Campus Store, 1955-1970; 146464 (Box 1a, Folder 9)
  - Campus Store Board of Control, 1974-1976; 146465 (Box 1a, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, 1971-1979; 146466 (Box 1a, Folder 11)
  - Curriculum Reform- Media Studies Program, 146467 (Box 1a, Folder 12)
  - Draft and Military Counseling, 1970-1972; 146468 (Box 1b, Folder 13)
  - Elections, 1978-1994; 146469 (Box 1b, Folder 14)
  - Escort Service, 1985-1988; 146470 (Box 1b, Folder 15)
  - Exams, Mid-Year, 1951-1967; 146471 (Box 1b, Folder 16)
  - Exams, Self-Scheduled, 1971-1978; 146472 (Box 1b, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Contract Renewal, 1963-1970; 146473 (Box 1b, Folder 18)
  - [Charlie] Freeman Case, 1969; 146474 (Box 1b, Folder 19)
  - Freshman Week, 1963-1981; 146475 (Box 1b, Folder 20)
  - Hackerman- Senior Talk, 1973; 146476 (Box 1b, Folder 21)
  - Housing On-Campus, 1962-1967; 146477 (Box 1b, Folder 22)
  - ICSA Proposal, 1981; 146478 (Box 1b, Folder 23)
  - ICUT, 1970-1974; 146479 (Box 1b, Folder 24)
  - [John L. Wortham] Insurance, 1976-1980; 146480 (Box 1b, Folder 25)
  - Keys, 1978; 146481 (Box 1b, Folder 26)
  - Legal Aid, 1974; 146482 (Box 1b, Folder 27)
  - Legal Aid Advisory Group, 1975-1979; 146483 (Box 1b, Folder 28)
  - Student Bail Fund (Legal Aid), 1961; 146484 (Box 1b, Folder 29)
  - Newsclips, 146485 (Box 1b, Folder 30)
  - Officer Rosters, 1971-1988; 146486 (Box 1b, Folder 31)
  - Organizations/Activities Fair, 1981; 146487 (Box 1c, Folder 32)
  - Owl Care Fund, 1983; 146488 (Box 1c, Folder 33)
  - Parking, 1965-1967; 146489 (Box 1c, Folder 34)
  - Referendum for SA Treasurer, 1985; 146490 (Box 1c, Folder 35)
  - Resolutions Passed, 1970-1971; 146491 (Box 1c, Folder 36)
  - Rice Memorial Center Expansion, 1982-1984; 146492 (Box 1c, Folder 37)
  - Rules and Regulations Development, 1963-1967; 146493 (Box 1c, Folder 38)
  - Salaries/Scholarships, 1967-1968; 146494 (Box 1c, Folder 39)
  - Sammy's, 1963; 146495 (Box 1c, Folder 40)
  - Speakers, 1970-1976; 146496 (Box 1c, Folder 41)
  - SA Office, 1983; 146497 (Box 1c, Folder 42)
  - SA Office Secretary, 1970-1976; 146498 (Box 1c, Folder 43)
  - SA Treasurer, 1983-1985; 146499 (Box 1c, Folder 44)
  - Traffic and Parking Regulations, 1974; 146500 (Box 1c, Folder 45)
  - Travel Funds, 146501 (Box 1c, Folder 46)
  - Vending Machines, 146502 (Box 1c, Folder 47)
- Series II: Committees, 1963-1982; 146521
  - Standing committees, 1987-1988, 146522 (Box 2a, Folder 1)
  - Standing committees correspondence, 146523 (Box 2a, Folder 2)
  - Standing committee reports, 146524 (Box 2a, Folder 3)
  - Standing committee reports, 146525 (Box 2a, Folder 4)
  - Standing committee rosters, 146526 (Box 2a, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Academic Affairs (Self-Study), 146527 (Box 2b, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Academic Calendar Reform, 146528 (Box 2b, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Academic Planning, 146529 (Box 2b, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Admissions, 146530 (Box 2b, Folder 9)
  - Committee: Alumni-Student Liaison, 146531 (Box 2b, Folder 10)
  - Committee: Athletics, 146532 (Box 2b, Folder 11)
  - Committee: Campus Store Advisory, 146533 (Box 2b, Folder 12)
  - Committee: Computers, 146534 (Box 2b, Folder 13)
  - Committee: Constitution, 1970s; 146535 (Box 2b, Folder 14)
  - Committee: Convocation, 1975-1976; 146536 (Box 2b, Folder 15)
  - Committee: Curriculum, 146537 (Box 2b, Folder 16)
  - Committee: Education Council, 146538 (Box 2b, Folder 17)
  - Committee: [Report of the Student Committee on] Educational Policy, 1963-1964; 146539 (Box 2b, Folder 18)
  - Committee: [Report of the Student Committee on] Educational Policy, 1964-1965; 146540 (Box 2b, Folder 19)
  - Committee: [Report of the Student Committee on] Educational Policy, 1967; 146541 (Box 2b, Folder 20)
  - Committee: Student Committee on Educational Policy, A New Plan for Undergraduate Education at Rice University, 146542 (Box 2c, Folder 21)
  - Committee: Examinations and Standing, 146543 (Box 2c, Folder 22)
  - Committee: Finance, 1958-1980; 146544 (Box 2c, Folder 23)
  - Committee: Finance, 1981-1988; 146545 (Box 2c, Folder 24)
  - Committee: Finance, correspondence, 1980-1983; 146546 (Box 2c, Folder 25)
  - Committee: Financial Aid, 146547 (Box 2c, Folder 26)
  - Committee: Food/Dining, 146548 (Box 2c, Folder 27)
  - Committee: Housing, 146549 (Box 2c, Folder 27a)
  - Committee: Intercollegiate Athletics, 146550 (Box 2c, Folder 28)
  - Committee: Library, 146551 (Box 2c, Folder 28)
  - Committee: Managerial Studies Steering, 146552 (Box 2c, Folder 30)
  - Committee: Minority Affairs, 146553 (Box 2c, Folder 30a)
  - Committee: NROTC, 146554 (Box 2c, Folder 30b)
  - Committee: Off-Campus Students, 146555 (Box 2c, Folder 31)
  - Committee: Publications, 146556 (Box 2c, Folder 32)
  - Committee: Public Lectures, 1975-1976; 146557 (Box 2c, Folder 33)
  - Committee: Registrar's, 146558 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Committee: Residential College Management Advisory Board, 146559 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Committee: [Permanent class] Ring, 146560 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Committee: ROTC, 146561 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Committee: Safety, 146562 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Student Affairs, 1976-1982; 146563 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Student Health, 146564 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Student Rights, 146565 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Undergraduate Affairs, 146566 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Committee: Undergraduate Curriculum, pre-1970, 1971-1972; 146567 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Committee: Undergraduate Summer Program, 146568 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Committee: Undergraduate Teaching, 146569 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Committee: University Governance, 146570 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Series III: Constitution and Bylaws, 1938-1993; 146571
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1938-1967, 146572 (Box 4a, Folder 1)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1959-1960, 146573 (Box 4a, Folder 2)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1960s, 1960-1969; 146574 (Box 4a, Folder 3)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1964-1968, 146575 (Box 4a, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1967-1972, 146576 (Box 4a, Folder 5)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1968-1974, 146577 (Box 4a, Folder 6)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, November 1, 1974, 146578 (Box 4a, Folder 7)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, April 7, 1975, 146579 (Box 4b, Folder 8)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, September 15, 1975, 146580 (Box 4b, Folder 9)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1975-1976, 146581 (Box 4b, Folder 10)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1975-1979, 146582 (Box 4b, Folder 11)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1982-1988, 146583 (Box 4b, Folder 12)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, March 1992, 146584 (Box 4b, Folder 13)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, Revisions, 146585 (Box 4b, Folder 14)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1993-, 146586 (Box 4b, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Correspondence and Memos, 146587
  - Correspondence: 1957-1958, 146588 (Box 5a, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: 1958-1959, 146589 (Box 5a, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: 1959-1960, 146590 (Box 5a, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: 1960-1961, 146591 (Box 5a, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: 1961-1962, 146592 (Box 5a, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Received, 1962-1963, 146593 (Box 5a, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence out, 1962-1963, 146594 (Box 5b, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence received, 1963-1964, 146595 (Box 5b, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence out, 1963-1964, 146596 (Box 5b, Folder 9)
  - Senate meeting correspondence, 1963-1964, 146597 (Box 5b, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence received, 1964-1965, 146598 (Box 5b, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence out, 1964-1965, 146599 (Box 5b, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: 1965-1966, 146600 (Box 5b, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: 1966-1967, 146601 (Box 5b, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: 1967-1968, 146602 (Box 5c, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: March-October 1970, 146603 (Box 5c, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: November-December 1970, 146604 (Box 5c, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: January-March 1971, 146605 (Box 5c, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: April-December 1971, 146606 (Box 5c, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: 1972-1973, 146607 (Box 5c, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: 1974-1975, 146608 (Box 5c, Folder 21)
  - Senate correspondence, 1974-1979, 146609 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: 1975-1976 (Folder 1), 146610 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: 1975-1976 (Folder 2), 146611 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: 1978-1980, 146612 (Box 6, Folder 3a)
  - Correspondence: 1982-1985, 146613 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Memos: 1969-1970, 146614 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Memos, 146615 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Memos: 1983-1984, 146616 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Memos: 1984-1985, 146617 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Memos and Email, 1993-, 146618 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Series V: Financial, 146619
  - Blanket Taxes, 146620 (Box 7a, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 1965-77, 1965-1977; 146621 (Box 7a, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1980-84, 1980-1984; 146622 (Box 7a, Folder 3)
  - Endowment, 146623 (Box 7a, Folder 4)
  - Financial, 1969-70, 1969-1970; 146624 (Box 7a, Folder 5)
  - Financial, 1971-1972, 146625 (Box 7a, Folder 6)
  - General Notebook, 146626 (Box 7a, Folder 7)
  - Financial Aid policies and procedures, 146627 (Box 7a, Folder 8)
  - Income statements, 146628 (Box 7a, Folder 9)
  - Ledgers, 1956-57, 1965-67, 1956-1967; 146629 (Box 7a, Folder 10)
  - Ledgers, 1971-72, 1973-74, 1975, 1975-76, 1971-1976; 146630 (Box 7b, Folder 11)
  - Ledgers, 1972-73, 1972-1973; 146631 (Box 7b, Folder 12)
  - Ledgers, 1977-78, 1978-79, 1977-1979; 146632 (Box 7b, Folder 13)
  - Ledgers, 1982-84, 1984-86, 1982-1986; 146633 (Box 7b, Folder 14)
  - Ledgers, 1977-78, 1978-79, 1980, 1981-82, 1977-1982; 146634 (Box 7b, Folder 15)
  - Statements, 1978-79, 1978-1979; 146635 (Box 7c, Folder 16)
  - Texas Commerce Bank account statements, 1985-88, 1985-1988; 146636 (Box 7c, Folder 17)
  - Merrill Lynch account, 146637 (Box 7c, Folder 18)
  - Merrill Lynch statements, 146638 (Box 7c, Folder 19)
  - Student Organization Financial Statements, 1962-80, 1962-1980; 146639 (Box 7c, Folder 20)
  - Tax exempt status, 1970, 146640 (Box 7c, Folder 21)
  - Treasurer general information, 1987-88, 1987-1988; 146641 (Box 7c, Folder 22)
- Series VI: Judicial, 146642
  - Judicial procedures development, 146643 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Judicial procedures with academic regulations and grievance procedure draft, 146644 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Judicial system review, 1984-1985; 146645 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Judiciary, 146646 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Series VII: Organizations, 146647
  - SA Affiliate organizations list, 1976-1980; 146648 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Club Constitutions, 146649 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Aikido Club, 1980; 146650 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - AICE (American Institute of Chemical Engineers), 1974-1979; 146651 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - ASME (American Society of Mechanical Engineers), 1971-1977; 146652 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Amnesty International, 1980-1981; 146653 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Baha'i Fellowship, 1975-1978; 146654 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ballroom Dance Society, 1977-1979; 146655 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1975-1976; 146656 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Biology Graduate Student Association, 1974-1979; 146657 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Black Student Union, 1971-1976; 146658 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ, 1974-1975; 146659 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Canterbury Association, 1974-1975; 146660 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Chabad (Jewish Students), 1980; 146661 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - [Rice University] Chorale, 1974-1977; 146662 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Christian Science Organization, 1974-1979; 146663 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Christian Students, 1975-1976; 146664 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Council on Future Affairs, 146665 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Czech Club, 1979; 146666 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - [Rice] Dance Troupe, 1982; 146667 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Debate Club, 1975-1979; 146668 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - [Rice] Democratic Caucus, 1976-1980; 146669 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Disco Society, 1978; 146670 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - The Eclectic Reader, 1979; 146671 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Eta Kappa Nu, 146672 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Fellowship of Christian Athletes, 146673 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - [Rice] Fencing Club, 1982; 146674 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Field Hockey Club, 146675 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - [Ultimate] Frisbee Club, 1982; 146676 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Gay/Lesbian Support Group, 146677 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Girl Scouts, 146678 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Hillel, 1971-1979; 146679 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Honor Council, 146680 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - IEEE, 146681 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Inter-College Council Minutes, 1957-1959; 146682 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Intercollege Court, 146683 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - International Folk Dancers, 146684 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 146685 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - [Cascade] Juggling Club, 146686 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Karate Club, 146687 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - [Japanese] Karate Club, 146688 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - KTRU: Financial, 1968-1983; 146689 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Lacrosse Club, 146690 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Libertarian Association, 146691 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Literary Societies, 146692 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - [Students International] Meditation Society, 146693 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - [Association of] Mexican-American Students, 146694 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Minority, general, 146695 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Oriental Culture Club, 146696 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Oxfam Group, 146697 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 146698 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Phi Delta Phi, 146699 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Phi Lambda Upsilon, 146700 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Philosophy Club, 146701 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - [Society of] Physics Students, 146702 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Pre-Business Society, 146703 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Pre-Law Association, 146704 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Pre-Med Society, 146705 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Psi Study Group, 146706 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Psychology Club, 146707 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Radio Club, 146708 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Rally Club, 146709 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Rappelling Club, 146710 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Religious, general, 146711 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Rice University Fund, 146712 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Rugby Club, 146713 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Running Club, 146714 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Sailing Club, 146715 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Scuba Club, 146716 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - [NROTC] Sextant Club, 146717 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Shooting Sports Club, 146718 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Skydiving Club, 146719 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - [Men's] Soccer Club, 146720 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - [Women's] Soccer Club, 146721 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Sports Club Program, 146722 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - [Rainbow Rockers] Square Dance Club, 1974-1979; 146723 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Tau Beta Pi, 146724 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - TexPIRG, 146725 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Tutoring Project, 146726 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - University Council, 146727 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Volleyball Club, 146728 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Waterpolo Club, 146729 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Weightlifting Club, 146730 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Wrestling Club, 146731 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 146732 (Box 9, Folder 85)
- Series VIII: Pub, 149690
  - Alcoholic Beverage Policy, 1965-1971; 149691 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Control Board General, 1974-1982; 149692 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Control Board Minutes, 1975-1983; 149693 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Financial, 1975-1984; 149694 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - History, 1974-1978; 149695 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Operation Committee, 1978-1982; 149696 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Series IX: Publications, 149697
  - Campanile: Financial Reports, 1961-1981; 149698 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Campanile: General, 1966-1983; 149699 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Fowl, 1972; 149700 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Janus, 1972; 149701 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Newcomer's Guide, 1972-1986; 149702 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Publication Rack, 1972; 149703 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Senate Journal, 1973; 149704 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Student Directory, 1967-1987; 149705 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Student Handbook, 1970; 149706 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Thresher: Case, 1977-1978; 149707 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Thresher: Financial, 1958-1983; 149708 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Thresher: Gen. Info., 1977; 149709 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Thresher: Poll on College Masters, 1971; 149710 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Series X: Colleges, 149711
  - Baker, 1964-1987; 149712 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Brown, 1970-1971; 149713 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Coed, 1971-1973; 149714 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Coed, 1970-1972; 149715 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - College Pres. Report, 1969-1970; 149716 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - General, 1970-1973; 149717 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Handbook, 1972; 149718 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Hanszen, 1973; 149719 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Jones, N.D.; 149720 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Libraries, 1965; 149721 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lovett, 1969-1976; 149722 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Masters, 1968-1970; 149723 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Open House Policy, 1962-1971; 149724 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Relations, 1982-1983; 149725 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Richardson, 1971; 149726 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Wiess, 1973-1974; 149727 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Will Rice, 1960; 149728 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Series XI: Rice Program Council, 149729
  General Note
  More specific information about the Rice Program Council can be found in the Rice Program Council records.
  - General, 1973-1984; 149732 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Series XII: Minutes, 149735
  - Student Association Dec - May, 1918-1930; 149736 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Student Association Sept - Feb, 1930-1936; 149737 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Student Association Sept - Mar, 1936-1938; 149738 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Student Association Sept - May, 1938-1939; 149739 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Student Association Sept - May, 1938-1940; 149740 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Student Association Sept - May, 1940-1942; 149741 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Student Association Sept - May, 1942-1943; 149744 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Student Association July - Feb, 1943-1944; 149745 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Student Association Apr - May, 1944-1945; 149746 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Student Association July - Feb, 1945-1946; 149748 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Student Association May - May, 1947-1948; 149749 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Student Association Sept - May, 1948-1949; 149750 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Student Association May - Apr, 1949-1950; 149751 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Student Association Apr - May, 1950-1951; 149752 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Student Association May - Apr, 1951-1952; 149753 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Student Association, 1952-1953; 149754 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Student Association, 1953-1954; 149755 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Student Association, 1954-1955; 149756 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Student Association, 1955-1956; 149757 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Student Association, 1956-1957; 149758 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Student Association, 1958-1959; 149759 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Student Association, 1959-1960; 149760 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Student Association, 1960-1961; 151589 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Student Association, 1961-1962; 151590 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Student Association, 1962-1963; 151591 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Student Association, 1963-1964; 151592 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Student Association, 1964-1965; 151593 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Student Association, 1965-1966; 151594 (Box 16, Folder 6)